<resources>
    <string name="app_name">First Aid</string>
    <string name="whatToDo">Important Topics:</string>
    <string name="textview">Seizures</string>
    <string name="textview1">How To Prepare a basic First Aid Kit</string>
    <string name="textview2">Cuts</string>
    <string name="textview3">Burns</string>
    <string name="textview4">leninism</string>
    <string name="textview5">Marxism</string>
    <string name="textview6">Socialism</string>
    <string name="textview7">Communism</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="button">Sand</string>
    <string name="LabelTopic1">Seizures</string>
    <string name="LabelTopic2">How To Prepare a basic First Aid Kit</string>
    <string name="LabelTopic3">Cuts</string>
    <string name="LabelTopic4">Burns</string>
    <string name="LabelTopic5">leninism</string>
    <string name="LabelTopic6">Marxism</string>
    <string name="LabelTopic7">Socialism</string>
    <string name="LabelTopic8">Communism</string>
    <string name="LabelAbout">About</string>
    <string name="Large_Text1">
       "If you witness a seizure, try to keep the"
 " calm down and before anything else call an"
        " emergency service. Pay close attention to what happens "
		"during and after the crisis.\n\n"

"During a seizure:\n\n"

"Protect the person from injury"
"Try to rest the person gently on the floor"
        ", if it shows signs of falling"
"Try moving away furniture or other objects that"
        "may injure the person during the seizure"
"If the person having a seizure is already "
        "on the floor when you arrive, put something soft under your head"
"Do not force anything, including your fingers, into the person's mouth."
        " Placing something in the person's mouth can cause injury to him or her,"
        "like chipped teeth or a fractured jaw. You could also be bitten"
"Turn the person to your side, with your mouth down, unless the person resists being moved"
"Do not attempt to release or shake the person"
"If person vomits, turn person to side."
"Pay close attention to what the person"" is doing so you can describe"" convulsion to the rescue or doctor:\n\n"

"What type of body movement occurred?"
"How long did the seizure last?"
"How did the person act immediately after the attack?"
"Are there injuries?\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="Large_Text2">
        "A basic first aid kit may contain:\n\n"

"1- plasters in a variety of different sizes and shapes "
"2- small, medium and large sterile gauze dressings "
"3- at least 2 sterile eye dressings "
"4- triangular bandages "
"5- crêpe rolled bandages "
"6- safety pins "
"7- disposable sterile gloves "
"8- tweezers "
"9- scissors "
"10- alcohol-free cleansing wipes "
"11- sticky tape "
"12- thermometer (preferably digital) "
"13- skin rash cream, such as hydrocortisone or calendula "
"14- cream or spray to relieve insect bites and stings "
"15- antiseptic cream "
"16- painkillers such as paracetamol (or infant paracetamol for children), aspirin (not to be given to children under 16), or ibuprofen "
"17- cough medicine "
"18- antihistamine cream or tablets "
"19- distilled water for cleaning wounds "
"20- eye wash and eye bath\n\n "
        "It may also be useful to keep a basic first aid manual or instruction booklet with your first aid kit.\n\n "
        "Medicines should be checked regularly to make sure they're within their use-by dates.\n\n "
    </string>
    <string name="Large_Text3">
        "Check the cut. If you can see fat, muscles or bones,"
"you probably need stitches. Check"
" the situation with a doctor if you are not sure."
"Signs of a problem that needs medical attention"
" may include any of the following: extreme pain "
", bleeding and signs of shock (cold, excessive sweating,"
" chills or pallor). To know if a cut"
" crossed the skin, try to observe the presence of "
" fat (irregular and yellow tissue), muscles "
" (fibrous and red tissue) or bones (surface "
" rigid and white). Points are not "
" necessary if the cut does not cross the skin. "
" Treat the injury at home.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="Large_Text4">
"The universal rule for burning by fire is to cease the source of the flames;"
" then use cold water to cool the affected area."
"This is the indicated output, since there are no"
" medication, product or homemade recipe  "
"to reduce the pain caused by a "
"burn or improve the injury."
"The famous ointments, even those available"
" in pharmacies, stress still"
" mais as células da pele, irritando-a e"
" causing infections. If bubbles appear, do not"
" blow them at all: they are"
" natural protection against burns."
" Bubbles are typical of second degree burns, "
"deeper, and should only be handled by a physician."
"Avoid wrapping the lesion with tissues"
" or cotton: they can stick."
"Accessories such as watches, bracelets, rings, laces"
" and earrings, on the other hand, should be withdrawn."
" This is because the human body tends to swell after suffering a burn and"
" these objects can get stuck."
    </string>
    <string name="Large_TextAbout">
        "Made by Hugo Lazzari and\n"
        "Agatha Cerqueira"
    </string>
</resources>
